export const quizInfo = {
    questions: [{
        question:
            "Can I park here?",
        choices: [
            "Sorry, I did that",
            "It's the same place",
            "Only for half an hour",
            "No, it is disappointing"
        ],
        type:
            "Understanding",
        correct:
            "Only for half an hour"
    },
    {
        question:
            "What colour will you paint the children's bedroom?",
        choices: [
            "It is hard to decide",
            "We have already coloured it",
            "I hope it was right",
            "It wasn't very difficult"
        ],
        type:
            "Understanding",
        correct:
            "It is hard to decide"
    },
    {
        question:
            "I can't understand this letter",
        choices: [
            "I suggest reading it first",
            "Would you like some help?",
            "Don't you read it?",
            "I am sure you can"
        ],
        type:
            "Understanding",
        correct:
            "Would you like some help?"
    },
    {
        question:
            "I'd like two tickets for tomorrow's concert",
        choices: [
            "How much did you pay?",
            "How much does it cost?",
            "Afternoon and evening",
            "I'll just check for you"
        ],
        type:
            "Understanding",
        correct:
            "I'll just check for you"
    },
    {
        question:
            "Shall we go to the gym now?",
        choices: [
            "I'm too tired",
            "Sorry, it is strange",
            "It's very good",
            "Never mind"
        ],
        type:
            "Understanding",
        correct:
            "I'm too tired"
    },
    {
        question:
            "His eyes were ...... bad that he couldn't read the number plate of the car in front",
        choices: [
            "so",
            "such",
            "too",
            "more"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "so"
    },
    {
        question:
            "The company needs to decide ...... and for all what its position is on this point.",
        choices: [
            "first",
            "last",
            "once",
            "all"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "once"
    },
    {
        question:
            "Don't put your cup on the ...... of the table - someone will knock it off",
        choices: [
            "outside",
            "border",
            "edge",
            "boundary"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "edge"
    }, {
        question:
            "I'm sorry - I didn't ...... to hurt you",
        choices: [
            "have",
            "think",
            "hope",
            "mean"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "mean"
    }, {
        question:
            "The singer ended the concert ...... her most popular song.",
        choices: [
            "with",
            "by",
            "on",
            "of"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "with"
    }, {
        question:
            "Would you mind ...... these plates a wipe before putting them in the cupboard?",
        choices: [
            "making",
            "giving",
            "to make",
            "to give"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "giving"
    }, {
        question:
            "I was looking forward ...... at the new restaurant, but it was closed.",
        choices: [
            "to eating",
            "to eat",
            "to have eaten",
            "eat"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "to eating"
    }, {
        question:
            "...... tired Melissa is when she gets home from work, she always makes time to say goodnight to the children.",
        choices: [
            "Whatever",
            "No matter how",
            "However much",
            "Although"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "No matter how"
    }, {
        question:
            "It was only ten days ago ...... she started her new job",
        choices: [
            "after",
            "that",
            "beforehand",
            "since"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "that"
    }, {
        question:
            "The shop didn't have the shoes I wanted, but they've ...... a pair specially for me.",
        choices: [
            "looked",
            "booked",
            "asked",
            "ordered"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "ordered"
    }, {
        question:
            "Have you got time to discuss your work now or are you ...... to leave?",
        choices: [
            "thinking",
            "planned",
            "about",
            "off"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "about"
    }, {
        question:
            "She came to live here ...... a month ago.",
        choices: [
            "almost",
            "after",
            "already",
            "before"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "almost"
    },
    {
        question:
            "Once the plane is in the air, you can ...... your seat belts if you wish",
        choices: [
            "faster",
            "unfasten",
            "unlock",
            "locker"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "unfasten"
    },
    {
        question:
            "I left my last job because I had no ...... to travel.",
        choices: [
            "place",
            "position",
            "opportunity",
            "possibility"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "opportunity"
    }, {
        question:
            "It wasn't a bad crash and ...... damage was done to my car.",
        choices: [
            "small",
            "little",
            "light",
            "bit"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "little"
    }, {
        question:
            "I'd rather you ...... to her why we can't go.",
        choices: [
            "explained",
            "will explain",
            "to exlain",
            "would explain"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "explained"
    }, {
        question:
            "Before making a decision, the leader considered all ...... of the argument.",
        choices: [
            "sides",
            "lines",
            "prospects",
            "features"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "sides"
    }, {
        question:
            "This new printer is recommended as being ...... reliable",
        choices: [
            "stongly",
            "intensively",
            "highly",
            "firepridely"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "highly"
    }, {
        question:
            "When I realised I had dropped my gloves, I decided to ...... my steps",
        choices: [
            "reject",
            "rewalk",
            "retrace",
            "revise"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "retrace"
    }, {
        question:
            "Anne's house is somewhere in the ...... of the railway station",
        choices: [
            "region",
            "district",
            "neighbourhood",
            "vicinity"
        ],
        type:
            "Use",
        correct:
            "vicinity"
    }
    ]
}